<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on IMP Portfolio</title>
    <link>http://www.students.oamk.fi/~t6loer00/imp_portfolio/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on IMP Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2018 22:42:27 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.students.oamk.fi/~t6loer00/imp_portfolio/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Lab 1</title>
      <link>http://www.students.oamk.fi/~t6loer00/imp_portfolio/posts/lab1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2018 22:42:27 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.students.oamk.fi/~t6loer00/imp_portfolio/posts/lab1/</guid>
      <description>1. Definitions:  HTML - Hypertext Markup Language, a markup language which is a standard for creating web pages. CSS - Cascading Style Sheets, a language used for creating layout and a presentation of web pages. Javascript - a programming language that defines behaviour of web pages. HTTP - Hypertext Transfer Protocol, an application-layer protocol used for transferring data between web browsers and servers. HTML5 - the current version of the Hypertext Markup Language.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lab 2</title>
      <link>http://www.students.oamk.fi/~t6loer00/imp_portfolio/posts/lab2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2018 22:42:32 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.students.oamk.fi/~t6loer00/imp_portfolio/posts/lab2/</guid>
      <description>1. Definitions:  What is the purpose of the RWD? Why it is used? How things are done before RWD? What is the difference?
Responsive Web Design technology helps to make web pages look good across all devices, such as desktops, tablets and mobile phones. It give a possibility to control the layout and reposition content according to device&amp;rsquo;s orientation and scale or hide necessary elements, such as images or menus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lab 3</title>
      <link>http://www.students.oamk.fi/~t6loer00/imp_portfolio/posts/lab3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2018 22:42:36 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.students.oamk.fi/~t6loer00/imp_portfolio/posts/lab3/</guid>
      <description>1. Web Sockets Web Socket technology allows a bidirectional communication between a client and server, which allows both sides to push data at any given time. It should be used in the applications where low-latency is crucial, like real-time applications or online games.
Link
 What happens if you send a message: ”LOGO”?
 HTML code for LOGO is returned  2. Local Storage A person list app redesigned according to Model–view–controller pattern and local storage is added, so the information is stored even if browser is reopened.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lab 4</title>
      <link>http://www.students.oamk.fi/~t6loer00/imp_portfolio/posts/lab4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2018 22:42:39 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.students.oamk.fi/~t6loer00/imp_portfolio/posts/lab4/</guid>
      <description>1. Very simple draw application A simple drawing application with canvas which tracks mouse movements and draws when the mouse button is released. The drawing is made using 2 canvasses, where the guideline is first visible on the &amp;ldquo;helper&amp;rdquo; canvas and then on the lower &amp;ldquo;drawing&amp;rdquo; canvas.
Link
2. Simple game A simple speed game made using canvas and Javascript with a time limit where the user has to click as many targets as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lab 5</title>
      <link>http://www.students.oamk.fi/~t6loer00/imp_portfolio/posts/lab5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2018 22:42:42 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.students.oamk.fi/~t6loer00/imp_portfolio/posts/lab5/</guid>
      <description>1. Getting familiar with jQuery  What you can do with the jQuery?
jQuery is the most widely used Javascript library that helps creating interactive websites and animations.
 How it can help you as web developer?
jQuery helps to perform a lot of daily web developer&amp;rsquo;s tasks with less code - creating animations, selecting DOM elements, developing AJAX applications. It also allows developers to create their own plug-ins.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lab 6</title>
      <link>http://www.students.oamk.fi/~t6loer00/imp_portfolio/posts/lab6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2018 22:42:45 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.students.oamk.fi/~t6loer00/imp_portfolio/posts/lab6/</guid>
      <description>1. Flickr photo wall A web application which connects to Flickr API to search for the information requested by a user and loads information with AJAX without reloading the rest of the page. Link</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>